{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_5_0DPCPO",
                "player_4_0DPCPO"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                5,
                4
            ],
            "animation": [
                "stand",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    1076.368,
                    -4171.126,
                    101.0,
                    0,
                    91.71967816743495,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -298.271,
                    -4869.812,
                    82.097,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_0DPCPO"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    225.651,
                    -5220.707,
                    282.097,
                    0,
                    -109.59973215115365,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "car": {
            "name": [
                "car_3_0DPCPO"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "None"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Yellow vehicle with black stripes, modern style, compact structure"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    424.28,
                    -4594.434,
                    82.097,
                    0,
                    -40.40639136113987,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "BP_Sedan_child_extras_C"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            745.414,
            -5151.39,
            82.328
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1281.001701289133
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone",
        "car"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -490.771,
            -4775.388,
            100.579,
            0,
            4.140257879173485,
            0
        ],
        [
            -478.535,
            -5604.756,
            82.097,
            0,
            46.83129262601547,
            0
        ],
        [
            1082.129,
            -4279.546,
            101.0,
            0,
            -149.07108393561057,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, Yellow_Car or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Yellow_Car",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Yellow_Car"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, Yellow_Car or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Yellow_Car",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Yellow_Car"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, White_Drone or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Drone",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, White_Drone or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Drone",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, Yellow_Car or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Yellow_Car",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Yellow_Car"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Drone, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Drone, Yellow_Car or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Yellow_Car",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Yellow_Car"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many human figures are present in the scene, considering their current actions?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many entities are engaged in the act of holding something?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many female individuals are visible in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many diferent colors of electric vehicles are present?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. sit",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. walk"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walk",
                    "B. holding_something",
                    "C. run",
                    "D. sit"
                ],
                "answer": "B. holding_something"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the the_woman_in_floral_shirt relative to the the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the front-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the the_woman_in_camo_vest relative to the the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. To the front-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the the_woman_in_camo_vest relative to the Yellow_Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the White_Drone relative to the the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the front-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the White_Drone relative to the the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the White_Drone relative to the Yellow_Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            }
        }
    }
}